Guide to the Carl E. Ladd papers,1932-1943
Ladd, Carl E. papers, 1932-1943
- Carl E. Ladd papers
  - Rockefeller Foundation., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - S Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Paul Smith Foundation., 1939-40 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    Betten, Cornelius; Horner, Harlan H.; Day, Edmund Ezra; Paul Smith's College.
  - State Schools., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - T Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    McAmis, J. Carl; Fertilizer.
  - Tompkins County Development Association., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Town Highway Superintendents' School., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - U Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    Upson, Maxwell M.
  - V Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    Van Wagenen, Jared Jr.
  - W Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Youth Conference., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    Culp, Claude L.
  - Governor of the State of New York., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    Lehman, Herbert H.; Poletti, Charles; Agricultural legislation.
  - Budget Director., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - New York State Dept. of Agriculture and Markets., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    Noyes, Holton V.; Dutch Elm Disease.
  - New York State Dept. of Conservation., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    Osborne, Lithgow; Bump, Gardiner; Ski trails.
  - New York State Dept. of Education., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    Weber, Abraham S.; Simpson, A.D.; Wilson, Lewis A.; Graves, Frank Pierrepont; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.
  - New York State Public Service Commission., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - New York State Division of State Planning., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    Heydecker, Wayne D.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    Wallace, Henry A.; Wilson, M.L.; Reed, O.E.; Ezekiel, Mordecai; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Dairy Industry; Maize Genetics Cooperation; Devon Cattle; Agricultural economics; Farmer-labor relations.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture, Office of Experiment Stations., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    Jardine, James T.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    Warburton, Clark; Brigham, Reuben.
  - Farm Security Administration., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    Montgomery, Edward G.
  - Soil Conservation Service., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    Huff, Albert N.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Plant Industry., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - New York State Agricultural Conservation Committee., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    New York State Security Advisory Committee.
  - Regional Research Laboratories., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    Lehman, Herbert H.; Jardine, James T.; Ithaca Chamber of Commerce; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Office of Experiment Stations.
  - Regional Research Laboratories., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - President's Office., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Day, Edmund Ezra; Ulbricht Fund.
  - Committee to Select President of University., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Cornell University Treasurer and Comptroller., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Rogalsky, George F.; Cornell Research Foundation.
  - Assistant Treasurer., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Office of the Dean., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Agricultural Economics and Farm Management., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Hart, Van B.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Economics and Farm Management; Grange League Federation; Milk industry.
  - Agricultural Engineering., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Engineering.
  - Agronomy., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agronomy.
  - Animal Husbandry., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Wallack, Walter; Morrison, Frank B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Animal Husbandry; A.I. Reed Farm.
  - Bailey Hortorium., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Botany., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    Wiegand, Karl M.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Botany; Broadcasting.
  - Business Office., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Entomology., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    Palm, Charles E.; Needham, J.G.; Tennessee Valley Authority; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Entomology.
  - Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    Guterman, Carl E.F.; Pearson Farm.
  - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    Parrott, Percival J.; Breed, Robert S.
  - Extension, Office of the Director., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    Simons, Lloyd R.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service; County agents.
  - New York State Farm Bureau Federation, State Leaders., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    Flansburgh, Earl A.; Milk strike.
  - New York State Home Bureau Federation, State Leaders., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - New York State Junior Extension, State Leaders., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    Wright, William J.
  - E.A. Bates., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    Bates, E.A.; Indian Agricultural Extension Service; Indian affairs.
  - L.D. Kelsey., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    Kelsey, Lincoln D.; Rural electrification; Soil erosion.
  - M.E. Robinson., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - C.A. Taylor., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Taylor, Charles A.
  - Farm Practice., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    Curtis, Ralph W.; Post, Kenneth; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture.
  - Drought Program., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Home Economics., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Hotel., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    Meek, Howard B.; Cornell University, School of Hotel Administration; F. & M. Schaefer Scholarship.
  - Forestry., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    Cope, Joshua A.; Society of American Foresters; Arnot Forest; Norris-Doxey Act.
  - Library., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    Ellis, Willard W.; Agricultural library.
  - Plant Breeding., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    Love, Harry H.; Babcock, Howard E.; Guterman, Carl E.F.; Emerson, Rollins A.; Grange League Federation; Puerto Rico Agricultural Experiment Station; Cucumber industry; Wheat crops.
  - Plant Pathology., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    Whetzel, Herbert H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Pathology.
  - Pomology., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    Oskamp, Joseph; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Pomology.
  - Poultry Husbandry., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    Heuser, Gustave F.; Romanoff, Alexis L.; Botsford, H.E.; Hutt, Frederick B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Poultry Husbandry.
  - Resident Instruction., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    Betten, Cornelius; Guise, Cedric H.
  - Rural education., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    Butterworth, Julian E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Rural Education; George-Deen funds.
  - Rural Sociology., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    Sanderson, Dwight; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Rural Sociology.
  - Vegetable Crops., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    Thompson, Homer C.; New York State Vegetable Growers Association; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Vegetable Crops.
  - Zoology., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    Allen, Arthur A.; Albert R. Brand Bird-Song Foundation.
  - Music Department., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    Weaver, Paul J.; Rockefeller Foundation.
  - Graduate School., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    Clinton DeWitt Smith Fellowship.
  - Engineering., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    Hollister, Solomon C.; Cornell University College of Engineering.
  - Arts and Sciences., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    Stainton, W.H.; Cornell University College of Arts and Sciences.
  - Miscellaneous Committees., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Committee on State Budget., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Publications Committee., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Agricultural Library Committee., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Committee on Program and Function of State College Council., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    Babcock, Howard E.; Agricultural legislation.
  - Arboretum., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    Weatherlow, Hugh E.; Wells, Nelson Miller; Civilian Conservation Corps; Arnot Forest.
  - Budget Requests., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Farm and Home Week, 1940., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    Lehman, Herbert H.; Farm and Home Week.
  - Correspondence Regarding Applicants for Admission, Agriculture, Home Economics., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    Weber, Abraham S.; Day, Edmund Ezra; Graves, Frank Pierrepont; Noyes, Holton V.; Byrd, Harry F.; Lipsky, David E.; Anti-semitism.
  - Traveling Fellowships., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - New York State Agricultural Society., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    Knapp, Halsey B.
  - Applications for Positions., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - American Agriculturist., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - A Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - B Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    Buck, John Lossing; Byrd, Harry F.; Beneway, Frank W.; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc.
  - Bermuda Survey., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    Spurling, Stanley; Bermuda Board of Agriculture.
  - H.E. Babcock., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - C Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - D Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    Dean, Daniel; Donlon, Mary H.; Deering, Arthur L.
  - Dartington Hall., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - John Dewey School Project., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    Stone, Candace.
  - Empire State Potato Club., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Empire State Gas and Electric Association., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    Burgan, John L.; New York State Gas and Electric Corporation.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    Firestone, Harvey S.
  - American Farm Bureau Federation., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - New York State Farm Bureau Federation., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Farm Credit Administration., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    Thomson, Edward H.; Lamb, George W.; Federal Farm Mortgage Corporation; Federal Land Bank; Foreclosures.
  - G Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    Gage, Simon Henry.
  - New York State Grange., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - National Grange., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Grange League Federation., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - General Motors - Cornell World Price Index., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - H Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    Institute of Rural Affairs.
  - New York State Home Bureau Federation., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - School for Highway Superintendents., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    Goodman, Alpheus M.; New York State College of Agriculture.
  - I Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - J Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - K Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - L Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Creel, Cecil W.; Bankhead-Jones Act.
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Walton, T.O.; Brigham, Reuben; Warburton, Clark; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service; New York State Cooperative Extension Service; Farm Forestry Act; Agricultural Experiment Stations.
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities, Executive Committee., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Walton, T.O.; Creel, Cecil W.; Agricultural legislation.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - T.E. Milliman., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Milliman, Thomas E.; Devon Cattle.
  - Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers Bargaining Agency., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Norton, Ralph S.; Milk marketing.
  - N Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - New York State Bankers Association., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - New York Farmers, Inc., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Appleton, Francis R.
  - Near East Foundation, Agricultural Council., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Ober, Frank W.
  - O Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - P Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - R Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Rockwell, George H.; Ranney, Florence J.; Rice, James E.; Cornell Plantations.
  - S Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Smith, Paul; Sears Roebuck Agricultural Foundation.
  - T Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    Thorne, Samuel.
  - Tennessee Valley Authority., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    McAmis, J. Carl; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service; Fertilizer.
  - U Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - V Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - W Miscellaneous., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    New World Resettlement Fund for Spanish Refugees.
  - World's Poultry Congress., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    Rice, James E.; United States Egg and Poultry Magazine.
  - WGY Farm Forum., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Governor of the State of New York., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Lehman, Herbert H.; Poletti, Charles; Farm and Home Week; Agricultural legislation.
  - New York State Dept. of Agriculture and Markets., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    Crumb, C.R.; Noyes, Holton V.; Crouch, H.E.
  - New York State Dept. of Education., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    Graves, Frank Pierrepont; Homer, Harlan H.; George-Deen Fund.
  - Budget Director., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - New York State Dept. of Conservation., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    Osborne, Lithgow.
  - Comptroller., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    Tremaine, Morris S.
  - New York State Public Service Commission., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    Bucknam, R.F.; Farm and Home Week.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    Wilson, M.L.; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Devon Cattle.
  - Extension Service., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Wilson, M.L.; Brigham, Reuben; Eisenhower, Milton S.; Warburton, Clark; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; Four-H Clubs.
  - Office of Experiment Station., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    Jardine, James T.; Winters, R.Y.; Trullinger, R.M.; Wallace, Henry A.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Office of Experiment Stations; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Bankhead-Jones Act.
  - Bureau of Plant Industry., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    Auchter, E.C.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Plant Industry.
  - Farm Security Administration., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    Georgia, Willard E.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Farm Security Administration; Agricultural legislation.
  - Soil Conservation Service., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    Jones, John P.; Pasto, Tuure A.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service.
  - United States Weather Bureau., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    Reichelderfer, Francis W.
  - Federal Plant, Soil, and Nutrition Laboratory., 1939-40 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    Auchter, E.C.; Weatherlow, Hugh E.; United States Regional Plant, Soil, and Nutrition Laboratory; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Bankhead-Jones Act.
  - President's Office., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    Day, Edmund Ezra; Parrott, Percival J.; Babcock, Howard E.; Cornell University, School of Hotel Administration; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.
  - Provost's Office., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    MacDaniels, Laurence H.; Peters, H.W.; United States Nutrition Laboratory.
  - Cornell University Secretary., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    Graham, Edward K.
  - Buildings and Grounds., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Cornell University Treasurer and Comptroller., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    Trousdale, James B.; Rogalsky, George F.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.
  - Cornell University Assistant Treasurer., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Business Office., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    Peterson, Arthur H.
  - Appointments, Resignations, etc, Report to the President., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Office of the Dean., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Agricultural Economics and Farm Management., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    Catherwood, Martin P.; Myers, William I.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Economics.
  - Agricultural Engineering., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    Riley, Howard W.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Engineering.
  - Agronomy., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    Bradfield, Richard; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agronomy.
  - Animal Husbandry., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    Morrison, Frank B.; McCay, Clive M.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Animal Husbandry.
  - Bailey Hortorium., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Botany., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    Wiegand, Karl M.; Knudson, Lewis; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Botany.
  - Dairy Industry., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Dairy Industry.
  - Entomology., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    Palm, Charles E.; Griswold, Grace H.; Hood, Joseph D.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Entomology.
  - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    Parrott, Percival J.; Guterman, Carl E.F.; Nebel, Bernard R.; Wellington, Richard; Tukey, Harold B.; Tressler, Donald K.; New York State Fruit Testing Association; Japanese Beetle.
  - Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    Guterman, Carl E.F.; TVA Superphosphate.
  - Extension, Office of the Director., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    Simons, Lloyd R.; Sanderson, Dwight; Wilson, M.L.; New York State Emergency Agricultural Defense Committee; New York State Cooperative Extension Service.
  - Farm Practice., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    Day, Edmund Ezra; MacDaniels, Laurence H.; Williams, H. Hamilton; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture.
  - Forestry., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Plant Breeding., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    Emerson, Rollins A.; Rockefeller Foundation; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Breeding.
  - Plant Pathology., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Pomology., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Poultry Husbandry., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Resident Instruction., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    Gibson, Anson W.
  - Rural Education., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Vegetable Crops., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    Thompson, Homer C.; Hardenberg, E.V.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Vegetable Crops.
  - Rural Sociology., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Zoology., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    Hutt, Frederick B.
  - Hotel Administration., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    Meek, Howard B.; Statler Foundation; DuBois Soap Company Scholarship.
  - Home Economics., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    Eddy, Martha H.; Henry, Mary F.; Rose, Flora; Conference Board of Women's Educational Organizations.
  - Home Economics., 1940-41 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    Donlon, Mary H.; New York State College of Home Economics.
  - Correspondence Regarding Applicants for Admission, Agriculture and Home Economics., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Henry, Mary F.; Poletti, Charles; Weber, Abraham S.
  - Arboretum Committee., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Artificial Breeding Project., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    New York State Farm Bureau Federation; Holstein-Friesian Association of America.
  - Cross-Breeding Project., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Weatherlow, Hugh E.; United States Dept. of Agriculture; Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station.
  - Grazing Project, Mt. Pleasant Area., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Requests for Special Research or Extension Work., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Visual Aids., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Farm and Home Week, 1941., 1941 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Lehman, Herbert H.
  - New York State Soil Conservation Committee., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Peet, Harold L.; Kelsey, Lincoln D.; New York State Agricultural Conservation Committee; Arnot Soil Conservation Experiment Station.
  - Committee on Graduate Studies for Extension Workers., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Sanderson, Dwight; Betten, Cornelius.
  - Committee on State and County Fair Policies., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Calfhood Vaccination and Bang's Disease., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Dunn, Williams S.
  - New York State Agricultural Land Use Planning Committee., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - New York State Dept. of Agriculture and Markets., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Dunn, William S.
  - New York State Dept. of Education., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Wilson, Lewis A.; Furney, Oakley; Butterworth, Julian E.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    Slattery, Harry; Wickard, Claude R.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Rural Electrification Administration.
  - Office of Experiment Stations., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    Jardine, James T.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Office of Experiment Stations; School of Living; Bankhead-Jones Act; Rural electrification.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    Wilson, M.L.; Elmhirst, Leonard K.; National defense.
  - Farm Security Administration., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    United States Dept. of Agriculture, Farm Security Administration.
  - Soil Conservation., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    Pasto, Tuure A.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service.
  - New York State Division of State Planning., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Governor of the State of New York., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    Lehman, Herbert H.; Poletti, Charles; Farm and Home Week.
  - A Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - New York State Agricultural Society., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - American Agriculturist., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - American Institute of Cooperation., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - B Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    Benson, Ezra Taft.
  - Howard E. Babcock., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - C Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Dartington Hall., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - D Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Defense, General Folder., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    Lehman, Herbert H.; Davis, Chester C.; Federal Security Agency; National defense.
  - E Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Empire State Gas and Electric Association., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    Nixon, Maurice W.; Rural electrification.
  - Ford, Bacon and Davis, Inc., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    Van Phul, William; Beef cattle.
  - G Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - National Grange., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - General Motors Corporation., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Grange League Federation., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    Babcock, Howard E.; Milliman, Thomas E.; McConnell, James A.; Yellow Rocket.
  - H Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    Holland, Jerome H.